♪Just wanna say hello♪
♪ فقط أريد أن أقول مرحبًا ♪
♪Hello♪
♪ مرحبا ♪
♪You are so unstoppable♪
♪ أنت لا يمكن إيقافك ♪
=Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2= =Episode 31=
= Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2 = = الحلقة 31 =
Leave now.
ارحل الآن.
Or I'll tell the police you are trespassing.
أو سأخبر الشرطة أنك تتعدى على ممتلكات الغير.
Xiangxiang, why would you do that?
شيانغشيانغ ، لماذا تفعل ذلك؟
We are employees here.
نحن موظفون هنا.
Even the police can't do anything to us.
حتى الشرطة لا تستطيع فعل أي شيء لنا.
Right?
حق؟
Right.
الصحيح.
Besides, we...
الى جانب ذلك ، نحن ...
Don't touch me.
لا تلمسني.
Leave right now.
غادر حالا.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Xiangxiang, Sihan.
شيانغشيانغ ، سيهان.
Hide in the kitchen! Come on!
اختبئ في المطبخ!  هيا!
No.
رقم.
We are here to work.
نحن هنا للعمل.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Xiangxiang.
شيانغشيانغ.
Grandpa.
الجد.
Your auntie told me
أخبرتني عمتك
that your relatives are here.
أن أقاربك هنا.
Where are they?
أين هم؟
I want to meet them.
اريد مقابلتهم
They...
أنهم...
Hello, master.
مرحبا سيد.
I'm Yun Xiangxiang's auntie.
أنا عمة يون شيانغشيانغ.
This is her cousin.
هذا ابن عمها.
Now we are families.
الآن نحن عائلات.
Mr. Fu is your grandson.
السيد فو هو حفيدك.
Bingbing is your grandson too.
Bingbing هو حفيدك أيضًا.
Call grandpa, Bingbing.
استدعاء الجد ، Bingbing.
Hurry.
عجل.
Grandpa.
الجد.
Xiangxiang.
شيانغشيانغ.
What is this?
ما هذا؟
Grandpa...
الجد ...
Boss.
رئيس.
You really didn't have to
أنت حقا لم يكن لديك
go all the way to buy it this early.
يذهب كل الطريق لشرائه في وقت مبكر.
Their stinky tofu is the most famous here.
التوفو النتن هو الأكثر شهرة هنا.
But they don't have delivery service.
لكن ليس لديهم خدمة توصيل.
Xiangxiang will be very happy
سيكون Xiangxiang سعيدا جدا
when she sees this.
عندما ترى هذا.
Boss.
رئيس.
I really can't
أنا حقا لا أستطيع
stand the scent anymore.
تحمل الرائحة بعد الآن.
It stinks so much.
ينتن كثيرا.
That's everything
هذا كل شئ
that happened.
الذي حدث.
I'm not the daughter of the Yun family.
أنا لست ابنة عائلة يون.
I used that identity
لقد استخدمت تلك الهوية
to marry into your family.
للزواج من عائلتك.
But Sihan,
لكن سيهان ،
he has nothing to do with it.
لا علاقة له بها.
They like each other so much.
هم يحبون بعضهم البعض كثيرا
Nothing else matters.
لا شىئ اخر يهم.
Now that we will be families,
الآن بعد أن أصبحنا عائلات ،
we won't charge you
لن نفرض عليك رسومًا
for the patent invention.
لاختراع براءة الاختراع.
We can start the business together.
يمكننا بدء العمل معًا.
Wait, mom.
انتظري يا أمي.
You can't do that.
لا يمكنك فعل ذلك.
It's my patent.
إنها براءتي.
I have to charge for it.
يجب أن أتقاضى مقابل ذلك.
I have the final say.
لدي القول الفصل.
No.
رقم.
I'm the one to decide...
أنا من يقرر ...
Shut up, you two.
اخرسوا ، أنتما الاثنان.
Dad.
أب.
I don't think it's that simple.
لا أعتقد أن الأمر بهذه البساطة.
Yun Xiangxiang is just an ordinary girl.
يون شيانغشيانغ مجرد فتاة عادية.
It can't be so easy to pretend to be a high-born.
لا يمكن أن يكون من السهل التظاهر بأنك مولود.
There must be someone else behind this.
يجب أن يكون هناك شخص آخر وراء هذا.
Yun Xiangxiang,
يون شيانغشيانغ
who told you to do this?
من قال لك أن تفعل هذا؟
I did everything
لقد اتممت كل شئ
by myself.
بنفسي.
Fu Sihan has nothing to do with it.
فو سيهان لا علاقة له به.
Grandpa.
الجد.
Everything she said is true?
كل ما قالته صحيح؟
Listen to me, grandpa.
استمع إلي يا جدي.
The whole thing
الأمر بأكمله
started because of me.
بدأت بسببي.
It has nothing to do with Xiangxiang.
لا علاقة له بشيانغشيانغ.
No, grandpa, it's all because of me.
لا ، جدي ، كل هذا بسببي.
Not Sihan.
لا سيهان.
Don't say anything, Xiangxiang.
لا تقل أي شيء ، Xiangxiang.
Stop! All of you!
قف!  كلكم!
Don't be mad, grandpa.
لا تغضب يا جدي.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
أنا آسف.  هذا كله خطأي.
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
I'm tired.
أنا مجهد.
Miss Yun.
ملكة جمال يون.
Just go.
فقط اذهب.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
you are not welcome here.
أنت غير مرحب بها هنا.
Grandpa!
جدي!
Dad!
أب!
Doctor!
طبيب!
Hurry!
عجل!
Call the doctor!
اتصل بالطبيب!